Welcome to this seller university module.
In this video, we'll discuss what to do if you encounter error code 5885 when trying to add or edit
a product in the Amazon store.
Error code 5885 means you cannot change a product detail page, add offers on another seller's generic
product or copy the product detail page to another store.
To resolve this, we recommend creating a new product listing for a generic unbranded product.
If you believe you are complying with Amazon's policies, you can contact selling partner support
by navigating to help, then get help and resources.
Select adding a product followed by received an error code or message and then select your error
code.
If you're using an inventory file template, provide the Batch ID of the processing report in addition
to the ASIN.
If you're using Batch IDs for feeds, be sure to add one ASIN in the top field.
A member of Selling Partner Support will reach out if next steps are necessary.
Thank you and happy selling in the Amazon store!